gptengine.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Pixelior

####### White Label Guarantee

\- We guarantee that all information that you've shared with us will remain confidential.

\- We will never contact your clients or the clients of your clients.

####### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, fill out a form or Send Us an email.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or State, ZIP Code. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

####### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * • To personalize your experience: (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * • To improve our website: (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * • To improve customer service: (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

  * • To send periodic emails: The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request.

  * • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

####### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information.

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information or SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

####### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

####### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

####### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website, click here.

####### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

####### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on  **3/23/2013.**
